// This is the array of questions for the quiz, where the number, question, answer and options are passed
const questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: `"You Know the expression it’s been a pleasure... well it hasn’t." -?`,
    answer: "Mike Ehrmantraut",
    options: [
      "Mike Ehrmantraut",
      "Domingo Molina",
      "Theodore Beneke",
      "Elliot Schwartz"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: `"Yeah, totally Kafkaesque" -?`,
    answer: "Jesse Pinkman",
    options: [
      "George Merkert",
      "Tuco Salamanca",
      "Jesse Pinkman",
      "Steven Gomez"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: `"Chemistry is the study of matter, but I prefer to see it at the study of change." -?`,
    answer: "Walter White",
    options: [
      "Henry Schrader",
      "Walter White",
      "Marco & Leonel Salamanca",
      "Gale Boetticher"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: `"You don’t need a criminal lawyer. You need a criminal lawyer" -?`,
    answer: "Jesse Pinkman",
    options: [
      "Mrs. Pinkman",
      "Wendy S.",
      "Donald Margolis",
      "Jesse Pinkman"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: `"Mas his death satisfy you." -?`,
    answer: "Gus Fring",
    options: [
      "Victor",
      "Gus Fring",
      "Huell Babineaux",
      "Jane Margolis"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: `"Yo 148, 3-to-the-3-to-the-6-to-the-9. Representin’ the ABQ. What up, biatch? Leave it at the tone!" -?`,
    answer: "Jesse Pinkman",
    options: [
      "Gustavo Fring",
      "Gretchen Schwartz",
      "Jesse Pinkman",
      "Bogdan Wolynetz"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: `"Tread lightly." -?`,
    answer: "Walter White",
    options: [
      "Walter White",
      "Skinny Pete",
      "Saul Goodman",
      "Tomás Cantillo"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: `"I'm waiting for the cancer to come back." -?`,
    answer: "Skyler White",
    options: [
      "Francesca Liddy",
      "Adam Pinkman",
      "Theodore Beneke",
      "Skyler White"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: `"Funyuns are awesome." -?`,
    answer: "Jesse Pinkman",
    options: [
      "Theodore Beneke",
      "Jesse Pinkman",
      "Christian Ortgea",
      "Cynthia"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: `"Some people are immune to good advice." -?`,
    answer: "Saul Goodman",
    options: [
      "Lydia Rodarte-Quayle",
      "Skinny Pete",
      "Saul Goodman",
      "Marie Schrader"
    ]
  },
];